

CONTACT ME

501 297 401

mar.bogucki@gmail.com

https://marbogucki.github.io/

in marcin-bogucki-a96a8672

LANGUAGES

O English - B1

HOBBIES

- Nutrition & Cooking
- Job-related Literature
- ⊙ Sport gym, volleyball
- Cinema Star Wars

Marcin Bogucki

Front-end Developer

A demanding job as a Front-end Developer will enable me to combine both my academic knowledge and practical skills. Willing to be a member of a professional team to improve job-related skills while gaining working experience, especially JavaScript, React JS and Angular JS.



EXPERIENCE

2017-01 / today

5 mths (Gdansk) LPP

Junior Front-end Developer

Websites: Reserved, Mohito, Sinsay, Cropp, House.

2014-03 / 2016-12 2 years and 10 mths (Pruszkow) DaVinci Medical System

Web Designer, Front-end Developer

Interfaces web application, preparation of HTML and CSS code for medical applications.

2013-04 / 2014-03 1 year (Gdansk) Etendard Sp. zo.o.

Junior Front-end Developer

Website, online shops and web application (HTML adn CSS template creation).

2010-10 / 2013-03 2 years and 6 mths (Warsaw) Grupa Wsparcia Projektów Inwestycyjnych

Web Designer HTML/CSS Developer

Website design and building templates (HTML and CSS).

2010-06 / 2012-09 2 years and 4 mths (Warsaw) Education Media House
XHTML/CSS Developer

HTML/CSS Developer

Creating templates electronic diary for schools.

2008-09 / 2010-05 1 year and 9 mths (Warsaw)) Go Studio

Creating Website templates and online stores.



EDUCATION

2016 • info Share Academy

Junior Front-end Developer Training

2015 - 2016 • English Unlimited

B1 level

2014 • Eduweb

Responsive Web Design

2006-2007 Post-secondary school TEB Edukacja

Graphic Designer

Course in teaching and methodology, IT training

qualifications

2003-2008 • University of Warmia and Mazury in Olsztyn

MSc Technical-Information Education

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Sass, Bootstrap, RWD Scrum, Git, Jira, Confluence, Github, Bitbucket
 PhpStorm, Visual Studio Code, Phtoshp, Illustrator
- React JS, Ecma Script 6
 Webpack 2, Gulp
- InDesign, Magento, MySQL

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my application to be processed for the purposes of the recruitment process under the Personal Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997, consolidated text: Journal of Laws 2016, item 922 as amended.